<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>openNASA</title><link href="/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="/feeds/misc.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>/</id><updated>2011-07-27T09:05:00-04:00</updated><entry><title>No title [4019]</title><link href="/4019" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2011-07-27T09:05:00-04:00</updated><author><name>Nick Skytland</name></author><id>tag:,2011-07-27:4019</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;About Open Government [caption id=&amp;#8221;attachment_2874&amp;#8221; align=&amp;#8221;alignnone&amp;#8221;
width=&amp;#8221;170&amp;#8221; caption=&amp;#8221;The Hubble Space Telescope captured the swirling
galaxies of Arp 194, which forms this cosmic question mark.&amp;#8221;][/caption]
&lt;span class="caps"&gt;NASA&lt;/span&gt; is expanding transparency, participation, and collaboration and
creating a new level of openness and accountability. We are focusing on
embedding open government into three integrated aspects of our
operations—policy, technology, and culture. Whether &lt;span class="caps"&gt;NASA&lt;/span&gt; is using social
networks to allow students to interact directly with astronauts, or
creating a Cloud Computing Platform to give unprecedented access to
scientific data, we have embraced the Open Government Directive.
Highlights of &lt;span class="caps"&gt;NASA&lt;/span&gt;’s Open Government Activities &lt;span class="caps"&gt;NASA&lt;/span&gt;’s founding
legislation in 1958 instructed &lt;span class="caps"&gt;NASA&lt;/span&gt; to “…provide for the widest
practicable and appropriate dissemination of information…” The
principles of open government have been embedded in our operations for
50+ years. We recognize that open government is a process rather than a
product, and have taken a continuous-learning approach. &lt;span class="caps"&gt;NASA&lt;/span&gt;’s Open
Government activities span 22 identified Agency projects across the
centers, and 3 flagship initiatives will take the Initiative to a new
level: Policy: &lt;span class="caps"&gt;NASA&lt;/span&gt; is working to make open source software development
more collaborative at &lt;span class="caps"&gt;NASA&lt;/span&gt; to benefit both the Agency and the public.
Technology: &lt;span class="caps"&gt;NASA&lt;/span&gt; Nebula, as the government’s&amp;nbsp;first…&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry></feed>